<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
		<name>Nano Repair Tech</name>
		<author>Ogre</author>
		<targetVersion>1.0.0</targetVersion>
		<description><![CDATA[<size=30><color=#ffa500ff>             —  NANO REPAIR TECH  —</color></size>

<size=16><b>Allows construction of Nano Repair Units which slowly consume power and fuel to repair apparel and weapons.</b></size>

<size=15><color=#1a8bffff>UNITS:</color></size>
• <color=#fffd43ff>Beds</color>
  ◦ (single, double, hospital) - repair equipped apparel / weapons while you sleep in them.

• <color=#fffd43ff>Shelves</color>
  ◦ (2x1, 1x1) - repair apparel / weapons stored on them.
  ◦ includes 1x1 regular shelf in addition to the 1x1 nano shelf, not sure why there isn't one 
    already in the base game


<size=15><color=#1a8bffff>INFO:</color></size>
• The rate at which repair work is done is determined by the quality of the nano unit. and 
  is displayed in the info section.
• Units that are powered off still do their base functionality (ie you can still sleep in 
  beds, and store things on shelves that are not powered/fueled)
• When not actively repairing anything, nano units automatically go into low power 
  consumption mode.
• Fuel is consumed at a relatively slow rate. 1 Fuel heals 4 HP. During my testing around 
  1 fill up per year.
• Fuel is initially created at the machining bench, and with further research at the 
  refinery from unwanted apparel (including tainted). 
• Shelves repair at the same rate over 24 hours as beds do for 8 hours. i.e. if you sleep 
  all night with a duster on, the amount of repair done to it by a bed would have been the 
  same as if it had been on a shelf all day
• Shelves are particularly useful by a stockpile. Set the allowed HP range from 0-99 and 
  pawns will automatically take items off the shelf when they are fully repaired, and put 
  something else on that needs repaired.


<size=15><color=#1a8bffff>RESEARCH:</color></size>
• <color=#fffd43ff>Nano Repair Tech (basic tech):</color>
  ◦ This research allows construction of Nano Repair Units (beds / shelves). These basic 
    units will repair apparel only.

• <color=#fffd43ff>Apparel Breakdown:</color>
  ◦ Break down apparel (tainted and/or non-tainted), at the biofuel refinery into base Nano
    Tech chemicals. This break down process is very desctructive and the majority of useful
    chemicals are destroyed.

• <color=#fffd43ff>Nano Tech Refining:</color>
  ◦ Refine base Nano Tech chemicals with small amounts of textile or leather into Nano Tech 
    Fuel. This process requires chemfuel as a catalyst.

• <color=#fffd43ff>Nanite Extender Arm (weapons tech):</color>
  ◦ Alter the nanites used in nano tech units to incorporate an extender arm. This 
    modification, with an increased power requirement, makes it possible to repair
    weaponry in addition to apparel.

• <color=#fffd43ff>Power Shielding (advanced tech):</color>
  ◦ Further alter the nanites used in nano tech units to greatly increase their electric 
    shielding. This lets the nanites operate at higher wattages, increasing and repair 
    rate for apparel and greatly increasing their rate for weapons.


<size=15><color=#1a8bffff>CHANGES FOR v1.0:</color></size>
• The advanced tech no longer requires an entire new set of units to be made, the upgrades 
  are applied to the units after the research is complete. I did this because with an 
  advanced teir, it felt like a waste of resources to build the lower teir. With this change 
  the nano tech units are useful as soon as they are researched, and more research will make 
  them better without having to deconstruct/replace them.
• Renamed (Bending Beds -> Nano Repair Tech)
• The electricity only repair seemed too cheaty for a lot of people, even with the slow 
  repair rate. With the added fuel requirement it feels much more balanced.
• Added shelves
• Patched bulk traders so that they buy/sell nano tech fuel. It's market worth is roughly 
  that of wool, which isn't very much, but depending on how much you get raided, you could 
  end up with a lot of it via Apparel Breakdown research from dead raiders apparel.

<size=13><color=#ffa500ff>GitHub:</color> <color=#fdfca2ff>https://github.com/cmdprompt/NanoRepairTech</color></size>
<size=13><color=#ffa500ff>B18:</color> <color=#fdfca2ff>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1242508171</color></size>
]]>
		</description>
</ModMetaData>